Alphabetical Pamphlet Collection
University of Notre Dame Archives
- Alphabetical Pamphlet Collection: Printed Material, PALP
  - The Training of the Diocesan Superintendent / by Johnson, George Rev, 1920; PALP 8/12
  - Why Be Moral? / by Johnson, George Rev., PALP 8/13
  - The History of Salvation / by Johnston, Leonard, 1962; PALP 8/14
  - After All What is Law? / by Johnston, Lucian, PALP 8/15
  - After All, What is the State? / by Johnston, Lucian STL, c1920; PALP 8/16
  - Andrew D. White, PALP 8/17; Subject: Warfare of Science and Theology in Christendom
  - Freemasonry / by Johnston, Lucian, PALP 8/18
  - Martin Luther / by Johnston, Lucian, 1932; PALP 8/19
  - The Ways of St. Anthony / by Josephine, M. Sister, 1922; PALP 8/20
  - The Eucharistic Prayer - A Study of the Canon Missae / by Jungmann, J. A. SJ, 1956; PALP 8/21
  - What Shall We Do in Heaven? / by Kaler, P. A. CSSR, 1955; PALP 8/22
  - Education Versus Indoctrination / by Kallen, Horace M., 1934; PALP 8/23
  - The Seven Last Words Mass of the Presanctified / by Kalvelage, John A. CSSR, 1943; PALP 8/24
  - The Virgin Mother - Lenten Lecture, 1908 Part I and II / by Kane, R. SJ, 1921; PALP 8/25
  - Queen of Martyrs Pray for Us / by Keane, James R. OSM, 1938; PALP 8/26
  - Requiem Mass for our Holy Father, Pope Pius IX - The Providential Mission of Pius IX / by Keane, John J., 1878; PALP 8/27
  - VII. The Drink Question - Catholic Studies in Social Reform / by Keating, Joseph SJ, 1914; PALP 8/28
  - Christianity and "Woman's Rights" - Catholic Social Guild Pamphlets No. 16 / by Keating, Joseph SJ, 1912; PALP 8/29
  - Questions of the Day - CSG First Text Books - No. 3 / by Keating, Joseph SJ and Anselm Parker OSB, 1928; PALP 8/30
  - Outside and In / by Keeler, Floyd, 1936; PALP 8/31
  - Germaine "The Saint We Need" / by Keener, Joseph A., Msgr., 1954; PALP 8/32
  - The Holy Hour / by Keiley, B. J. DD, 1912; PALP 8/33
  - An Appeal / by Kelley, Francis C. Rt. Rev., c1919 ?; PALP 8/34; Subject: To Save the German Foreign Missions
  - Chivalry and Honor The Equestrian Order of the Holy Sepulchre of Jerusalem / by Kelley, Francis C. DD, 1941; PALP 8/35
  - The Mexican Question / by Kelley, Francis C. DD, 1926; PALP 8/36
  - Rhythm in Marriage Duty and Idealism / by Kelly, Gerald SJ, 1957; PALP 8/37
  - Modern Youth and Chastity / by Kelly, Gerald SJ, 1941; PALP 8/38
  - Father William Doyle SJ / by Hugh, Kelly SJ, 1935; PALP 8/39
  - Sex Questions the Right Answers to Teen-age Boys' / by Kelly, John R. SJ, 1956; PALP 8/40
  - Fruitful Days / by Kempf, Placidus OSB, 1945; PALP 8/41
  - The Acceptable Time / by Kempis, Thomas A., PALP 8/42
  - Thoughts on Holy Week / by Kempis, Thomas A., PALP 8/43
  - Freemasonry and Catholicism in America - The Catholic Mind / by Kenny, Michael SJ, 1914; PALP 8/44
  - The Onslaught of Scepticism / by Keppel Mother, 1934; PALP 8/45
  - What England Owed to France 1791 to 1802 / by Kerr, Cecil, 1929; PALP 8/46
  - Journeys to the Catholic Church No. 1 - In Quest of Faith and Why I am a Catholic / by Keeler, Floyd and John Meyer, PALP 8/47
  - Instructio Pro Confessariis / by Kiefer, Rt. Rev. Msgr. - Liederbach, Clarence Editor, PALP 8/48
  - The Sacraments - Signs of Christ, Sanctifier, and High Priest / by Kilmartin, Edward J. SJ, 1962; PALP 8/49
  - The Primacy of Peter - As Indicated in the Bible / by King, Francis, 1932; PALP 8/50
  - The Making of Men / by Kinkead, Eugene and Arthur V. Shea, 1959; PALP 8/51
  - Home ,School and Co. / by Kirsch, Felix M. OM, PALP 8/52
  - The Sex Problem / by Kirsch, Felix M. OM, 1935; PALP 8/53
  - American Research in Mediaeval Legal History / by Kisch, Guido, 1942; PALP 8/54
  - Juridical Lexicography and the Reception of Roman Law / by Kisch, Guido, 1944; PALP 8/55
  - Matrimonial Primer - A Handbook for Bride and Groom / by Klarmann, Andrew AM, 1915; PALP 8/56
  - A Brief History of Liturgy / by Klauser, Theodor, 1953; PALP 8/57
  - St. Augustine and the Deaf - The Catholic Educational Association / by Klopfer, Stephen Rev., 1912; PALP 8/58
  - The Beginning and End of Man / by Knox, Ronald A. MA, 1935; PALP 8/59
  - Catholicism - The Religion of Moderation and Common Sense / by Knox, Ronald Rev, PALP 8/60
  - Miracles / by Knox, Ronald Rev, 1928; PALP 8/61
  - The Passion / by Knox, Ronald A., Translator, 1944; PALP 8/62
  - A Papal Peace Mosaic 1878-1944 / by Koenig, Harry C. STD, PALP 8/63; Subject: Excerpts from the Messages of Popes
  - Religion and Communism in Africa / by Kolarz, Walter, 1962; PALP 8/64
  - Extreme Unction / by Krause, Joseph E., 1962; PALP 8/65
  - The Young Husband / by Kreuser Dr - Garahan, Isabel, Translator, 1933; PALP 9/01
  - Crusaders of Mary Immaculate - Children Crusade for Modesty / by Kunkel, B. Rev, 1950; PALP 9/02
  - Communism and the Catholic Answer / by LaFarge, John SJ, 1936; PALP 9/03
  - Integration Why? - Sign National Catholic Magazine / by O'Gara, James, 1958; PALP 9/04; Subject: The Catholic Interracial Movement and Fr. John LaFarge
  - Secularism's Attack on World Order / by LaFarge, John SJ - The Catholic Association for International Peace, 1944; PALP 9/05
  - The Catholic in Business / by Lahey, Thomas A. CSC, 1923; PALP 9/06
  - Catholic's Ready Reply / by Lahey, Thomas A. CSC, 1954; PALP 9/07
  - God's Heroes No. 1 Can Boys and Girls Become Saints? / by Lahey, Thomas A. CSC, 1935; PALP 9/08
  - God's Heroes No. 2 Children Saints / by Lahey, Thomas A. CSC, 1935; PALP 9/09
  - God's Heroes No. 3 Saints and Animals / by Lahey, Thomas A. CSC, 1935; PALP 9/10
  - God's Heroes No. 4 Saints Who Were Adventurers / by Lahey, Thomas A. CSC, 1935; PALP 9/11
  - God's Heroes No. 5 Other Saints Who Were Adventurers / by Lahey, Thomas A. CSC, 1935; PALP 9/12
  - God's Heroes No. 6 Hermit Saints / by Lahey, Thomas A. CSC, 1935; PALP 9/13
  - God's Heroes No. 7 Cheerfulness of the Saints / by Lahey, Thomas A. CSC, 1935; PALP 9/14
  - God's Heroes No. 8 Every-day Saints / by Lahey, Thomas A. CSC, 1935; PALP 9/15
  - God's Heroes No. 9 The Saints and Good Example / by Lahey, Thomas A. CSC, 1935; PALP 9/16
  - God's Heroes No. 10 Saints of High Position / by Lahey, Thomas A. CSC, 1935; PALP 9/17
  - God;s Heroes No. 11 Bravery of the Saints / by Lahey, Thomas A. CSC, 1935; PALP 9/18
  - God's Heroes No. 12 Suffering of the Saints / by Lahey, Thomas A. CSC, 1935; PALP 9/19
  - God's Heroes No. 13 Sympathy of the Saints / by Lahey, Thomas A. CSC, 1935; PALP 9/20
  - God's Heroes No. 14 Saints Who Were Sinners / by Lahey, Thomas A. CSC, 1935; PALP 9/21
  - God's Heroes No. 15 Saints Who Were Martyrs to Duty / by Lahey, Thomas A. CSC, 1935; PALP 9/22
  - God's Heroes No. 16 Women Saints / by Lahey, Thomas A. CSC, 1935; PALP 9/23
  - God's Heroes No. 17 Timid Saints / by Lahey, Thomas A. CSC, 1935; PALP 9/24
  - God's Heroes No. 18 Saints of Various Vocations / by Lahey, Thomas A. CSC, 1935; PALP 9/25
  - God's Heroes No. 19 Saints in Disguise / by Lahey, Thomas A. CSC, 1935; PALP 9/26
  - God's Heroes No. 20 Saints of the Future / by Lahey, Thomas A. CSC, 1935; PALP 9/27
  - Our Lady's Warning at Fatima / by Lahey, Thomas A. CSC, 1951; PALP 9/28
  - Notes on Ingersoll / by Lambert, L. A. Rev., 1900; PALP 9/29
  - You Can be Holy / by Lane, Clem, 1961; PALP 9/30
  - Two Lancashire Martyrs vv. John Rigby and Richard Herst / by Lane J. I. Rev., 1929; PALP 9/31
  - The Quakers / by Langdon D. M. J., 1926; PALP 9/32
  - The Spanish Church and Politics / by Langdon-Davies John, 1938; PALP 9/33
  - Catholic Schools / by Larkin, Michael J. Rev., 1927; PALP 9/34
  - How to be a Christian in Business / by Latchford, Stephen F. SJ, 1959; PALP 9/35
  - Inspiration / by Lattey, C. SJ, 1930; PALP 9/36
  - Revelation / by Lattey, C. SJ, 1930; PALP 9/37
  - His Last Retreat / by Lavall, William, 1922; PALP 9/38
  - What Every Family Should Know / by Le Beau, Walter, 1949; PALP 9/39; Subject: The Doctrine of the Mystical Body of Christ
  - The Death of the Cross a Physiological Study / by Le Bec, E. Dr., 1962; PALP 9/40
  - The Catholic Layman / by Missionary Society of St. Paul the Apostle, NY (Magazine), 1963; PALP 9/41
  - My Changeless Friend / by LeBuffe, Francis P. SJ, 1927; PALP 9/42
  - Broken Homes / by LeBuffe, Francis P. SJ, 1936; PALP 9/43
  - Human Evolution and Science / by LeBuffe, Francis P. SJ, 1922; PALP 9/44
  - Let's Look at Sanctifying Grace / by LeBuffe, Francis P. SJ, 1946; PALP 9/45
  - What is the Bible? / by LeBuffe, Francis P. SJ, 1943; PALP 9/46
  - Choice and Formation of Native Clergy in Foreign Mission / by Ledochowski, Wlodimir, SJ, 1919; PALP 9/47
  - How to be Humble / by Lee, Francise M. CSSR, 1955; PALP 9/48
  - Right to Work Laws: Some Economic and Ethical Aspects / by Lee, William James SS MA, 1961; PALP 9/49
  - Liturgie et Action Catholique / by Lefebvre, Dom Gaspar, 1961; PALP 9/50
  - Seven Last Words of Christ / by Lefebvre, Reginald R., SJ, 1961; PALP 9/51
  - What they Ask about Our Blessed Mother / by LeFrois, B., SVD, 1961; PALP 9/52
  - Towards the Eternal Priesthood / by Lelen, J. M. Rev, 1913; PALP 9/53
  - 1st English Printed Protestant Bible and its Significance / by Lenhart, John M. OMCap, 1935; PALP 9/54
  - Pope Leo XIII on Anglican Orders, 1932; PALP 9/55
  - Apostolical Letter of our Most Holy Lord Leo XIII Pope, 1899; PALP 9/56
  - Christian Marriage Encyclical Letter Pope Leo XIII - Arcanum Divinae Sapientiae, 1942; PALP 9/57
  - The Condition of Labor - Encyclical Letter of Pope Leo XIII, 1891; PALP 9/58
  - On the Sect of the Freemasons / by Encyclical Letter of Pope Leo the Thirteenth, 1884; PALP 9/59
  - On the Condition of Labor / by Encyclical Letter of Pop Leo the Thirteenth, 1891; PALP 9/60
  - Human Liberty Encyclical Letter of Pope Leo XIII - Libertas Humana, 1941; PALP 9/61
  - Pope Leo's Encyclical on the Condition of Labor, PALP 9/62
  - The Condition of Labor - Rerum Novarum / by Encyclical Letter of Pope Leo XIII, 1939; PALP 9/63
  - Encylical Letter of Pope Leo XIII on Condition of Labor / by Rerum Novarum, 1891; PALP 9/64
  - The Rosary and England's Ancient Love of Mother of God - Encyclical Letter Pope Leo XIII, 1883; PALP 9/65
  - The Unity of the Church / by Pope Leo XIII, 1949; PALP 9/66
  - A Questionnaire / by Lemmer, John A., PALP 9/67
  - The Legion of Mary / by Leonard CP, 1939; PALP 9/68
  - Religious Tolerance in Catholic Tradition / by Lercaro, Giacomo Cardinal, 1960; PALP 9/69
  - Catholics and the International Labor Organization / by Le Roy, Albert SJ, 1939; PALP 9/70
  - Thompson, Francis - Words Spoken in Washington Hall at the U of Notre Dame / by Leslie, Shane MA LLD, 1935; PALP 9/71
  - Dialogues of Defence: I - Infallibility, Anglican Orders, Fasting and Abstinence - The Celibacy of The Clergy / by Lester, Edmund SJ, 1928; PALP 9/72
  - Is There a True Church? / by Levy, Rosalie Marie, 1928; PALP 9/73
  - Why are We? / by Levy, Rosalie Marie, 1928; PALP 9/74
  - The Church of Jesus Christ - Where is the Church of Christ? How Shall I Know It? / by Lewis, William, 1950; PALP 9/75
  - Saint Teresa 1515 - 1582 / by Lewis, David, 1950; PALP 9/76
  - I was a Communist / by Liberov, Alexei B., 1936; PALP 9/77
  - When a Catholic Marries / by Liederbach, C. A., Rev., 1949; PALP 9/78
  - Life of the Spirit v. XVIII No. 204 / by The English Dominicans, Editors, 1963; PALP 9/79
  - Conformity to the Will of God / by Liguori, Alphonsus, Saint, 1928; PALP 9/80
  - Stations of the Cross / by Liguori, Alphonsus, Saint, 1894; PALP 9/81
  - The Liguorian v. XLIII No. 5 / by Redemptorists Fathers, 1955; PALP 9/82
  - Why be a Catholic? / by Lilly, Warren C., SJ, PALP 9/83
  - Father Isaac Joques - Among the Iroquois / by Little, Arthur SJ, 1924; PALP 9/84
  - A Youth Centre at Work / by LLoyd, Frances, 1942; PALP 9/85
  - The Church in Latin America / by Lochemes, Mary Frederick and McNamara Mary Patrice, 1945; PALP 9/86
  - Directives for Catholic Action - Expounded by Pope Pius XI / by Loeffler, James D. SJ, 1951; PALP 9/87
  - Housing for the Elderly / by Loeffler, James D. SJ, The Central Bureau of the Catholic Central Union Verei, 1960; PALP 9/88
  - Reveille in Christendom - A Summons to Catholic Action / by Loeffler, James D. SJ, 1934; PALP 9/89
  - Devotions in Lent / by Lonergan, William I. SJ, 1931; PALP 9/90
  - Did Man Make Religion? / by Lonergan, W. I. SJ, 1931; PALP 9/91
  - Do Miracles Happen? / by Lonergan, William I. SJ, 1931; PALP 9/92
  - The Story of Lent / by Lonergan, William I. SJ (Annotated), 1931; PALP 9/93
  - Ask Me Another / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1944; PALP 9/94
  - The Call of Christ - A Study of Religious Vocation for Young Men / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1927; PALP 9/95
  - The Call to Catholic Action / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1933; PALP 9/96
  - Christ the Modern / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1932; PALP 9/97
  - Don't Say It / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1929; PALP 9/98
  - Don't Swear Like That / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1943; PALP 9/99
  - Everybody's Talking About Heaven / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1935; PALP 10/01
  - Forever and Forever / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1936; PALP 10/02
  - Going Steady / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1941; PALP 10/03
  - His Strong and Loving Heart / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1954; PALP 10/04
  - How to Pray the Mass - Methods of Offering Our Sacrifice / by Lord, Daniel A., SJ, 1934; PALP 10/05
  - I Can Read Anything / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1930; PALP 10/06
  - I don't Like Lent / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1930; PALP 10/07
  - Is Religion Bad for your Mind? / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ - McCarthy, Raphael C. SJ, 1946; PALP 10/08
  - A Letter to our Non-Catholic Neighbors / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1950; PALP 10/09
  - Life of the Blessed Mother the Loveliest Mother of all / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, PALP 10/10
  - Love, Sex, and the Teen-Agers / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1947; PALP 10/11
  - May Your Christmas be Merry / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1945; PALP 10/12
  - My Faith and I / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1931; PALP 10/13
  - Prayers are always Answered / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1937; PALP 10/14
  - The Questions They Always Ask / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1943; PALP 10/15
  - The Ruling Passion / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1932; PALP 10/16
  - The Sacrament of Catholic Action / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1936; PALP 10/17
  - Are You Scrupulous? - An Interview with Francis J. O'Boyle SJ / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1937; PALP 10/18
  - Shall I be a Nun? / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1927; PALP 10/19
  - Spinsters are Wonderful People / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1947; PALP 10/20
  - A Talk on Girl Scouting / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, PALP 10/21
  - Truth's the Thing / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1930; PALP 10/22
  - What of Free Will? / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1935; PALP 10/23
  - When Mary Walked the Earth / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1929; PALP 10/24
  - When Sorrow Comes / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1931; PALP 10/25
  - Whose Country is This? / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1932; PALP 10/26
  - Why be Decent? / by Lord, Daniel A. SJ, 1938; PALP 10/27
  - What is Wrong? The World's Plight / by Losabe, John, PALP 10/28; Subject: Tendencies in Religion
  - For all the Feasts of the Blessed Virgin Mary - Liturgical Novenas and Triduums / by Lovasik, Lawrence G., Rev, 1946; PALP 10/29
  - Spiritual Check-up for the Unmarried / by Lovasik, Lawrence G. SVD, 1955; PALP 10/30
  - Credo / by Loyola, Mary Mother, 1925; PALP 10/31; Subject: Explanation of Christian Doctrine
  - The Magna Charta of the Rights of Labor - A Synopsis of Pope Leo XIII's Encyclical-Rerum Novarem / by Lucas, George J. JOD STD, c1891; PALP 10/32
  - The Iron Virgin of Nuremberg / by Lucas, Herbert SJ, 1928; PALP 10/33
  - The Catholic Booklist 1948 - Edited for the Catholic Library Association / by Luella, Mary OP and Claver, Mary Peter OP, PALP 10/34
  - The Catholic Booklist 1949 - Edited for the Catholic Library Association / by Luella, Mary OP, PALP 10/35
  - Is the Catholic Church an Enemy to Science? / by Lummer, Reginald CP, 1922; PALP 10/36
  - St. Gabriel of our Lady of Sorrows / by Lummer, Reginald CP, 1920; PALP 10/37
  - The Heavenly Court / by Saint Lutgarde of Brabant, c1943; PALP 10/38
  - A Quarter Century of Effort and Achievement 1916 - 1941 / by Lutz, Bernard E., PALP 10/39; Subject: The National Catholic Women's Union
  - Consecration Verse of a Priest / by Lynk, Frederick M. SVD, PALP 10/40
  - Mary Our Mother / by Lynk, Frederick M. SVD, 1951; PALP 10/41
  - The Renegade Home / by Lynch, Ella Frances, 1940; PALP 10/42
  - The United Nations Charter / by Mahony, Thomas H. and Post-War World Committee - A Report of the Post-War World Committee, 1945; PALP 10/43
  - The Christian Manifesto / by Dietz, Peter E., Rev, 1912; PALP 10/44
  - The Marianist / by Society of Mary, Cincinnati Province, 1944/04; PALP 10/45
  - Apostolate to Assist the Dying / by Markham, Raphael J. Rev., 1932; PALP 10/46
  - Apostolate to Assist the Dying / by Markham, Raphael J. STD, 1936; PALP 10/47
  - You Can Change the World / by Maryknoll Fathers, c1940; PALP 10/48
  - Science and the Catholic Tradition / by McMullin, Ernan, Rev., 1960; PALP 10/49
  - On Being Cheerful - Design for Living Series No. 5 / by McSorley, Joseph, of the Paulist Fathers, PALP 10/50
  - The Catholic Mind / by Muench, Aloisius J. - De La Bedoyere, Michael - Meath, Gerard OP - Rose, Golden, 1941; PALP 10/51
  - The Catholic Mind / by Ryan, Arthur H. DD - Desvernine, Raoul - Kelly, William A., 1942; PALP 10/52
  - The Catholic Mind / by McNicholas, John T. OP STM - Murray, John - Barnard, George - Hael, Ivor, 1942; PALP 10/53
  - The Catholic Mind / by McGohey, J. F. X. - Mulcahy, R. E. SJ - Farley, James A., 1942; PALP 10/54
  - The Catholic Mind / by Murray, Thomas E. - Dunne, G. H. SJ - van Kersbergen, L. Dr. - Masse, B. L. SJ - Pius XII - Cardinal van Roey, 1952; PALP 10/55
  - Catholic Mind / by Ewing, J. F. SJ - Senator Dodd - John XXIII - Archbishop O'Boyle, 1960; PALP 10/56
  - Salient Facts About N. C. W. C. (National Catholic Welfare Conference), c1927; PALP 10/57
  - Fourth National Conference on Catholic Youth Work - America's Hope - Youth with Faith / by Youth Department National Catholic Welfare Conference, 1953; PALP 10/58
  - German Nationalism and the Catholic Church / by Universe, 1917; PALP 10/59
  - Our Lady's Digest v.1 No. 1, 1946/05; PALP 10/60
  - Our Lady's Digest v.1 No. 3, 1946/07-08; PALP 10/61
  - Our Lady's Digest v. 1 No. 5, 1946/10; PALP 10/62
  - The Cross and the Flag v. 9 No. 4 - Christian Nationalism Defined, 1950/07; PALP 10/63
  - Pan Poetry and Youth v.II No. 2 / by O'Donnell, Charles L. CSC and Paul Harrington - Musser, Benjamin, 1926/03; PALP 10/64
  - Papal Directives for the Woman of Today / by Pope Pius XII, 1947; PALP 10/65
  - Christian Brothers Past Pupils Magazine / by Training College of the Christian Brothers, Dublin, PALP 10/66
  - Pastoral Life: a Publication for Priests, 1956/11-12; PALP 10/67
  - Paulist Fathers News v. 3 No. 6, 1963/06; PALP 10/68
  - Perspectives de Catholicite XIIIe Annee - No. 2 - Cahiers Des Auxiliaires, 1954; PALP 10/69
  - Perspectives de Catholicite 1957 - XVIe Annee - No. 3 - Etudiants Etrangers en Occident, 1958; PALP 10/70
  - Summi Pontificatus - Encyclical Letter Pope Pius XII - Exhorting Unity in Opposing World Evils (Annotated), 1939; PALP 10/71
  - The Fundamental Contradiction of Our Time - 1956 Christmas Message of Pope Pius XII, PALP 10/72
  - The Priest v. 14 No. 1 / by Our Sunday Visitor, Indiana, 1958/01; PALP 10/73
  - Essays on the Priesthood v. 11 No. 1 - St. Meinrad Essays, 1954/12; PALP 10/74
  - Pope Alexander VI. and his Latest Biographer - The Month / by Thurston, Herbert, 1925/04; PALP 11/01
  - Protest against Philippine Policy of Federal Government / by St. Paul's Parish Chicago, 1902; PALP 11/02
  - Opening Exercises for Public Schools / by Ferguson, E. E., 1891; PALP 11/03
  - The Rambler, a Catholic Journal and Review of Home and Foreign Literature, Science, Music and Fine Arts, 1853/07; PALP 11/04
  - Does Religion Matter in Marriage? (Liguorian Pamphlets), PALP 11/05
  - Your Eternity / by Remler, F. J. CM, PALP 11/06
  - AMDG Review for Religious - Renovation and Adaptation / by Gallen, Joseph F., 1955/11; PALP 11/07
  - St. Charles Borromeo Church 1873 / by D. M. Coleman, 1873-1973; PALP 11/08
  - M. Maddalena Bentivoglio of the Sacred Heart of Jesus - Foundress - Abbess - Order of St. Clare, 1834-1905; PALP 11/09
  - Mission / by Sheen, Fulton J. Bishop, Editor, 1956/01; PALP 11/10
  - Mission / by Sheen, Fulton J. Bishop, Editor, 1956/10; PALP 11/11
  - Slovakia v. II No. 3 / by Hrobak, Philip A., 1952/12; PALP 11/12
  - Catholic Social Teaching v. 1 No. 2 - No. 11 / by the Publicity Committee of the Catholic Social Guild, 1940-1941; PALP 11/13
  - Spiritual Life v. 9 No. 1 / by Discalced Carmelite Fathers, 1963; PALP 11/14
  - The True History of Maria Monk / by Stone, William L. Esq., 1836; PALP 11/15
  - The Conventual Life / by Right Rev. Bishop Ullathorne, 1914; PALP 11/16
  - The Message from Konnersreuth / by Rt. Rev. Sigmund Waitz, DD Bishop of Feldkirch - Benedictine Convent of Perpetual Adoration, Missouri, 1930; PALP 11/17
  - The Rosary and My Vocation / by Walsh, Nicholas E., Rev., 1956; PALP 11/18
  - The Truce of God / by Walsh, Edmund A., SJ, 1926; PALP 11/19
  - Blessed are they that Mourn / by Ward, Paul CSP, 1937; PALP 11/20
  - Marriage: a Dialogue on the Christian Ideal / by Ward, Wilfrid, Mrs., 1933; PALP 11/21
  - Relations Between France and Italy / by Ward, Patrick J. and the Europe Committee - Catholic Association for International Peace, 1934; PALP 11/22
  - The Truth About Catholics / by Ward, Joseph B Rev., 1942; PALP 11/23
  - Catholics and Communism / by The Catholic Social Guild, Oxford, 1925; PALP 11/24
  - Communism / by Watt, Lewis SJ, 1936; PALP 11/25
  - Communism and Religion / by Watt, Lewis SJ, 1937; PALP 11/26
  - The Ethics of Interest / by Watt, Lewis SJ, 1926; PALP 11/27
  - The Natural Rights of Man / by Watt, Lewis SJ - Catholic Social Guild, 1940; PALP 11/28
  - Pius XII and the War: Summary of the Encyclical Letter of Pope Pius XII "Darkness Over the Earth" / by Watt, Lewis SJ - Catholic Social Guild, 1940; PALP 11/29
  - The Way v.3 No. 3 / by Walsh, James, SJ, and William Yeomans SJ, 1963/07; PALP 11/30
  - Chaplains' Manual / by Weber, Gerard P., Rev., 1952; PALP 11/31
  - The Inside Story of God / by Weber, Sebastian OFM, 1941; PALP 11/32
  - What Do You Know about the Rosary? / by Wedge, Flarence, 1954; PALP 11/33
  - You and Your Patron Saints / by Wedge, M. F., 1955; PALP 11/34
  - Religious Customs in the Family / by Weiser, Francis X., SJ, 1956; PALP 11/35
  - Sing to the Lord and Bless his Name. ps. 95 / by Weller, Philip T., Rev, 1955/09; PALP 11/36
  - May a Catholic Be a Mason? / by Whalen, William J., 1960; PALP 11/37
  - Saint Margaret Mary the Pearl of Paray / by Wheaton, L., PALP 11/38
  - Confession of a Roman Catholic / by Whitcomb, Paul, 1958; PALP 11/39
  - The Enemy Within the Lines / by White, Patrick, 1943; PALP 11/40
  - The Religions of Scholasticism / by White, V. Rev. OP, 1934; PALP 11/41
  - Martin Luther / by Wiener, Peter F., PALP 11/42
  - 100 Questions on the Eastern Rites / by Wilcock, Feodor SJ, 1956; PALP 11/43
  - St. Bartholomew' Day (1572) / by Wilkinson, Maurice, 1933; PALP 11/44
  - Saint John Neumann Philadelphia's "Little Bishop" / by Wilson, Robert H., 1977; PALP 11/45
  - Dating a Guide for Parents / by Willcock, Ed., 1960; PALP 11/46
  - Catholic Rites and Pagan Customs / by Windle, Bertram Sir, 1928; PALP 11/47
  - Evolution and Catholicity / by Windle, Bertram C. A. Sir, 1925; PALP 11/48
  - Some Debts which Science Owes to Catholics / by Windle, Bertram, Sir, 1930; PALP 11/49
  - Bride and Groom / by Winters, C. M. Rev., PALP 11/50
  - It's A Woman's World / by Withey, Helen, 1951; PALP 11/51
  - Moral Disarmament and Catholic Schools / by Wolfe, John M., 1932; PALP 11/52